I am a special facility at the Fourth Board of Meetings, Monday and April for May 3,
but we want to see it.
We'll have the invitation, but that's actually a perfect strategy for the breaking of all of that.
It was great, thank you for just a beautiful day and just thank you for just the opportunity to live
in the third country and thank you for all your surrounding us, with your presence and thought
I was just worried that we are praying for community and I pray for our leaders and I pray that you can keep the wisdom
and I thought I'd only have to make some very difficult decisions and I just pray that if you would just go to the board
and get them all up in the evening and thank you for their service, thank you for their leadership
and I found this was our community in the age of always having Jesus and amen!
Also in the second.
No vote?
Not.
Or a bit.
You've got five.
Five.
Six.
Three.
Five.
Four.